dc-unlocker.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy policy | DC-unlocker.com

DC-Unlocker.com respects the privacy rights of those who visit our web site (DC-Unlocker.com).

Paragraphs bellow explain DC-unlocker. com privacy policy.

  * We do not collect personal information when you visit our site unless you create an account and make purchase.
  * When you create an account or buy at DC-Unlocker.com, depending from payment method you use, you will be asked for the following personal information: Your first and last name, country, e-mail address.
  * We do not share, sell, rent or barter any identifiable personal information to any third party in any way. Except if there is an official request from financial or government institutions.
  * We have newsletters available to inform you about DC-Unlocker.com news. You will be subscribed automatically after you create an account at DC-Unlocker.com. You may unsubscribe at any time by clicking on the "Unsubscribe" link in any newsletter You got from us.
  * When you contact DC-Unlocker.com via e-mail or by any other way, we may request personal information that you provided when created an account at DC-Unlocker.com.
  * We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user movement. We do not distribute or share IP information with any third parties. We do not link IP addresses to personally identifiable information or to username.
  * We take precautions to protect our customer's information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.
  * This website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that DC-Unlocker.com is not responsible for the privacy practices of these other sites. We encourage our users to be aware of when they leave our site, and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information.
  * DC-Unlocker.com website use cookies. Cookies are small pieces of information that are stored by your web browser on your computer's hard drive. A cookie file can contain information that the site uses to recognize something about you (such as your login name, or whether you've been to this site before or not). A cookie can't read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites. The only personal information a cookie contains is the information you provide yourself. Most web browsers by default accept cookies, but if you prefer, you can set your browser to block them. 

List of used cookies:

Name

Purpose

Expire time

More info

Used to distinguish users. 

Used to throttle request rate. 

Used by chat system (Providesupport.com) to allow communication with dc-unlocker.com staff. 

Set of cookies used by Google to protect you from malware (pref) and to store preferences (nid). Users can stop these cookies being set by turning off their browser’s ‘safe browsing’ mode. 

6 months

For further information on cookies and how to remove them, visit [ About Cookies: how to control cookies](http://www.aboutcookies.org/how-to-control-cookies/ "How to control cookies").

Please be aware that restricting cookies may impact on the functionality of dc-unlocker site.
